No. I have never said
that you are not good at what you do.
(Sheldon:)It's just that what you do
is not worth doing.
(Leonard:)It's nicer than anything
he's ever said to me. L'd take it and run.
(Howard:)Thank you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Will you give my paper to Hawking?
(Bernadette:)- Sorry, I can't.
- What? Why not?
l gave it to him three days ago.
(Howard:)He was really impressed.
(Howard:)He wants to meet you.
(Sheldon:)All right, then.
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Howard.
(Sheldon:)Please let Professor Hawking know...
(Sheldon:)...that I'm available
at his earliest convenience.
- Thought he might be more excited.
- Give it a second.
Professor Hawking, it's an honor
and a privilege to meet you, sir.